broadsides you are
actually
getting sucked up into your neighborhood
lived there for a couple for topics
panic
mark
iris
chuck
softballs
our thoughts
vault talking
spunky
software
already
class action
passing
has to go along
that section
test
ricky
suggestions spots
art
and has been changed fixing
it's fine
okay
secure ball
oxford st park yet
asking a question
yes
programs this fall apart
professor thatcher
fast
and one half minutes to watch
we have talked to me
acura
professor shwarier
pop
acct
partici
or uh... yeltsin's her
inside
object is persons to follow
allposters
so this time i have notes for you guys
if you want to have a lot because you're
going
this crazy world we want to use
if we didn't see me
if you go to
ebeneezer type wiki
this economy she
illegally
but don't follow that right away
we're gonna end up going
let's go higher see and i think if you
guys doing
so we'll get back to the saturday
but uh... start firefox but will go
ahead and jump into it and so on
the chancellor kohl and his appointment
for farm products
i want to meet you guys up and running
on this family cap so that
when someone is interested in the ask
the question there
cracker exactly
room to make sure everybody gets lost in
the setup
but the idea is
and in fact there are very artsy or
marcia's working
but you are a lot
to have a special
space
earlier on
so if you come back to this material
needed
now or
dude but focus on the catalogs
spots insight
and all the classes
surprises and confusing
you guys can
figure out what you think it's a that
if you want to
at something that you think is important
you guys inside
use that changed
i'm going to use a technique you guys
links
so articulate your help
for webpages
through that great sort you guys on the
morning
so they're gonna talks profitability
okay
firefox has
applauded
where you can capitalistic
and the first to know that you're going
to get
instructive
so i'll write appear to be accepted
researchers are excellent
you cannot come up
and
you could call me at all in sterling
and see something like this
but i think we could be active two
firefox unfortunate overreacted
had no time to go up move it
to put the add button
to see what does it need not worry dot
installed
cities your papa sitting
insult add-ons only for property trust
misses the point three point
restoring impediments from strange
people
strange things will happen to you
this one
jobs overseas by a lot of people it's a
very cinema all the ones i show you our
property
correction plugins are answer
ask write something
or ask how many sir
you think that if i think the body and
spirit to cellmark indictment check for
you
the particular install
vicky king is before arkansas flooded
it doesn't work
continue restore five
so i'm definitely confused beforehand
i've done a bunch of installs
come back how are you worried about his
past
and wondered why planet
obstruct our fox
confirm negotiated goes really fast
that top left corner of firefox
has died
the selenium
i could not find
and the plugins in here
asa someone those were the plugins arms
mood let me know i don't
but if you go to you
menu bar
so even if it for you guys
that many bars and change the work of
our fossil that get your menu across the
top
itself the coffin
subrident germany for details on that
it's gotten a section
cult schools
at the bottom of tools
design
canceled
and friends or something like this
and it's got a look
it should look exactly the same for
everybody except for
in the bottom left-hand corner only
it's going to say you were seekonk
shortens your
some wonderful name
that he wanted
and it's attached all your fault
so from there
we're gonna go ahead and
we're not talking to you
so great i receive works is there's no
sir
enters several
served in the world
anxious or responsible wanted
we're going to use her
spring on them
it's used by a lot of
open-source software offers end users
purple opens today
four opened software
and spoke three
how do you happen on the web
browser
then we can still insure honor channels
but we're gonna crescendo just for us
and since our classes opened you may or
may not see other people from other
places popping to want to know
interactive
you can always tell them
where to go ahead and walking through
the three of service member and join the
project
saucy guys how to
connection that so the command is
attacks
and this will be in the nazis
detach
piracy dot free of charge net
penner hopefully deteriorate
and she checked out
ends since it's a big connects tourists
we have in fact the passwords we haven't
seen anything about security
you're not walking through and making
the right
and it will be born
if you're if it happens is that do not
use any path
used anymore
it's obvious we're told that
it's meant to be easy
and it's not meant for secure
conversation
that if you want to be secure
conversations
soapbox and things like that
fair looks at
altman x-men
sharing and soon
distributor behavior
speak as if you're in public
and hold him up
so now we want to join
a doubt
so pick you up to you
higher seat
and joined channel
that's left join
and you should see something like it's
going to have a list of
uh... powers
so thick that illustrates
we want to join
you h
search
tools
which is very appreciated
i see a lot of people going this is
great
maybe you should see
policy of people that i see
and eighty-eight years is out
use the f_c_c_ tickets uh... don't want
if you go to
chat so uh... preferences
and they did not want
uh... option under general
their preferences
under general you can say
what was the year
it walked
the computer
and wants to tell wise
so you may be able to specify a opera
little things that were if they want to
but you can walk us and then through the
cardinals for the class so if somebody
gives you some diplomat
something that lucked out that you guys
think
someone knows
wants it just sharma
so what i can do for example is up
if i go to
research tools pots
i can now
i can paste that link
and hopefully on average three should be
i want to look at the time
network
if somebody wants more information
principles of a bargain
yea or go on something that
i'm talking about
active report
their ask questions
you can ask
you know answer the question
is totally ok
a couple of english
ran out what you want to say
and uh...
at her when you're comfortable with it
shutout phosphorylated
i'm hoping a really great
would you please
during medical was filled with people
thirteen at no
uh... the six of us
three months
living in a child's session like this
i'd never met
which is that
for fourteen hours a day
uh... it's a really eat all you can keep
it up
while you're working on the class
you guys can cooperate unit
some of you want to avert jerry or
internet he had people run shot
three groups on the flyer
for the rest of the semester walked into
that
this chap
it's the where is your participation
contract
expect to see at least one comments
approx
e-tickets
if you're headed their comments echo as
a you were in class
patsy kline
logged in
if you're here for research for stuff
like that
just let me know
will get to the chocolates and
yes
the log file is on your computer
someplace
if you look
under
preferences and then will be sentenced
and useful down here
fighting someone there and you can
change
microsoft word isn't it
unbelievable options that you can change
contingent workers for files
so if you have a shirt at your morning
or usb drive or something like that
salted almonds and share
puts up there
and just leave your hands
bc
drawer that's panicking that i used when
i'm working
and uh... allen sucked out my laptop
walked in
along the track there
in addition to
show where which is
me working on
laptop you guys so
i could have multiple instances of
myself going around
and you'll see that some people
various reasons to have
deferred tax agents that do different
things
people actually right
what software that goes in
and motivates
if we're working our class propaganda
and somebody expected
the software into the central server we
did see a message appeared here
it's ok so-and-so update
the line
this work for the file
dealership to do something
there's a lot of things need to do
because and watch the film rights and
starts later
they'll actually
software from command line put stuff
into this chat
so that what you see
power shift report
economist com
when shipped
over since the prubsn
when the weather center
upstairs
retractor or verbal assault rifles
it's a place where you can actually
write software
to give people notices
and just to let you know
this isn't the only with the software
around
there's lots of other ones out absent
listen here ones that
might work for you
if you're a mac user
there's a couple that are okay
there's also some less ones
had a chance to
but i think that what chancellor is if
you have firefox and ie
install plugin
you can count on the next
windows pcs
uh... use the same time tho
just to let you know there's lots of
other contracts
image this before
but i want to make sure you guys realize
that amputee heresy
and has to get you chatting with
other people outside boston
there's other channels there
reviews at school
syntel
which is four transformed into formats
the authors about software
criminalist prisoner there's almost
always someone
what's on that road
so if you want to talk to the author of
the software
this is the way to it
to be able to chat with the folks who
are actually building
discussions with them
etc to be quite and what i need to go
find out dot the one
i think i will show you
with this shack market one or two heart
attacks in
looks okay
units
but oftentimes it's better tastefully
some big market access a written up to
the source code
you want to share it with a bunch of
people
their services called concerts
there's a link grade here too
a particular piece system there's lots
of them
used any one of them that you want
i tended to use this one
law for any particular reason
it gives you scratch pad
so you can write whenever you want to
hear
nobody districts in jobs
or we could go over to
bickering and web page
so if we went over to
some wiki and
some junk
so we want to copy some code and i want
you guys to see it
we're going to go back to you
this feature tool
has been dot com
and extraordinaire
i can give its final
research tools
delivery counter three
out just remember again this is a public
service your piece on operatic
even if you mark a little private button
with people who can see the page three
thought was spam smith types of
characters
so what does it gives you this little
you are home
some copycat
effect over to check the oil
and i am pleased to hear
you guys are all elementary
and click on it
and we'll see what it was my patients if
you have something itself
coupler plans won't work center for and
discuss
leisurely
this is a really great to be viewed
uh... sometimes emails
statistical email system does not like
certain types of sports car coming
through the email because i think the
virus
you can't taste up into pieces
and sunday you'll one too
so if you're sharing little bits of text
secretly security
if the site for an accountant three
uh... as eighty percent record hasty
because of the systems that don't take
counts
and liberal repertoire except in cases
something
last year intemperate
we have a lot but here he says
pastry colors
satsuki here everybody
what's what
i want to wait for today
averages himself
but we're not going to do it
uses your voice
wrapped around the room
uh... abhijeet
operated everybody else here
part wanted to say hi
and what your forgiveness
on marcy
soldiers easygoing
yet mister backorder
is yourself
giveaways
and reworking opportunities that so i
apologize if that's true
openssl
you guys are going to have a colossal
for oracle dba
the storm outside her door
possible dates of this is a lot for your
lawyers out throughout the class
differences
you get asking a question of the
refugees sharply
so i'm sure you guys to see common
you'll love it here considerable
congratulate all so i can not
there's for himself
way ed
jumped a seat on the gate which is going
to be completely
and if you're outside its economy won't
be able to get to this
i what i want mostly tumbling
couple sessions
went out just
could only watch inside sleeping
this is our our goal here is the if
bases dot information that you
collecting the all-time or needed
virtually or every
once in a couple years
edits for all of us data and
work on this
there some pages that are
morgan has traded in the catholic not if
there was too much
western general if you walk really page
for anything
did you do for your research at work
it's a call
university or things that impacts didn't
like
this is a place where you can make pages
of links you can do
whatever you need to do
within constraints of putting american
so
you have to fit within
are guidelines that was in fact what's
the problem
that pretty much includes
most things in the chocolate
with people in the hallway
immediately starts
and especially enigma getting away with
computers and technology
it's a great place to documents
uh... how what the software
who talked with
certain tasks
let me also carefulness
the uh... i_t_t_ and if you ask a
question
they're gonna ask you to do look and we
can't work
and he didn't
you might guess i faced him in my
community within walking to the
community research first
ended the interview on there
it's up to us as people who work with
the phone order students here
to jump in and
to the wiki
so i mean you could drop this class too
create new response
amazing elected to experience
summer in a more formal but i'm working
towards being a book out
it's india
along form of the class
it's about three
outset notes
inside me a place that i want you guys
to be able to edit make comments tom
three pages as you work on tasks
for this lots of other classes
and i will be a was up a inside
so that you put to work
the first thing i want you all do
over here there's a lot of increase
account button
this thing is to provide security fence
what you can do is you can create
an account
has put recounts
there's nothing special about this
just go ahead typing using a packet of
password please do not need to see
column passport
we see something else
contact the statistic here
because they were getting kids he did
not want to be but would prefer that you
make heads
as your login
it tends to work basket issues remains
the same as pat buchanan chat session
in the same as usual using it
that way
a lot nicer as a community c_n_n_ it by
somebody to be able to find that person
if you tell us something about more
particular country won't
look you're from
knowledge
people want to come chat with you about
that
and follow up on it
imprints in discussion using a ticketing
them
it comes to that
tibetan for yourself account
and get yourself a lot in common go
ahead and login here
and if you look at pier report before
you appeared beofre notices and i p
address
uh... so what's right
what computer you on
if you're on a random when twenties
computer classroom wanted to make it
so i mean i want myself in
and so now look at it
you can always pleased at the
information
g_a_t_t_
when you make that it's double-check
robotic
we get a lot of pets
that's are not logged in
and it's hard to figure out what's going
on sometimes
they're changing its confusing
and only went
scintigraphy attitude
figure ph
that usually means that we don't
all
and that means is that
on the left ourself
help both links
and is not helpful institute rampage
i'm not really sure why that's helpful
it gives you a renovation wiki
uh... which is probably not very
interested to hear
if you're really bored because of their
income
random page link
i really
one of the best one citizen recent
changes especially after working in the
class on the material
you'll see
i tend to be
one of the biggest
heaviest values that we keep
kellysearch
uh... he was by doing that the wiki
exist so
internally by doing
you'll see
ill give you a couple options that the
difference
so i'll show you
uh... what changed between revisions on
future updates
in the view of history for that final c
concealed changes by whoever
we'll tell you who did it
there's a style section for talking
about that person's to that person
the p_l_o_'s contributions from that
person
you can see
so things are working
which is mostly research tools
right now it's xlost see you
people who are not seeking people
conduct will not get into it
and we ask
if you're not copy syntax
nancy come with the outside
when a person who wrote it to get their
permission
because the city residents
to be forty-four and the students here
so that if you are
nazi combat that includes you too
it's meant to be a resource inside
is not meant to be like wikipedia for
everybody
so if somebody wants to write something
that is a dresser public
it's okay to put stuff in here that's
masakela printed but we don't want to
look
if you're figuring something out what it
will be able to
uh... partial work
uh... thoughts
mason-dixon incorrect because you're
working on it
yeltsin to eliminate procedure four
it wasn't so
you have some ideas like three ideas you
don't want to check the world and want
to talk about insistent on
accepted
but because i decided to share with here
institutes
sitting in front of me
here since he does it not for me
cpc like yours george fabric working in
the ninety group
jordan setting up a server for s
freon is working on data logger system
so we can basic keep up with what's
going on c_-span sometimes reluctant
changes if you're working together marcy
with the latest and done
disney's placed upon
there is also
special pages on the left here
which gives you all kinds of funky but
he's stuff
and it's going to show you
you listed all the pages
self respect that
we have a lot of pages
they come along
but if you try to find something you
have
water to go to work
to uh... to use the differences are
thing you know
terminology you cannot figure into you
find something that might
meet your needs
like uh...
identified
which isn't very peacefully etc
how you can add to it
so it's a great place to scripting
through and find what kind of material
is on there
um... there's an important one
we have pages on ice skating
that uh... we have a tradition that
every year which involved at christie's
ice skating
it's a lot of fun
writes about the special pages
city peter here there's all kinds of
different stuff in here
constitute styx il tell u
gently parakeet
they'll tell you about that there's been
for sixty thousand
it is we have eleven thousand page and
it's
we have lots and lots of pages at five
hundred and five pages
and it really comes down to you
what you guys want
thank your that mostly pages the main
one of course
forum security by one person going
travel three travel forms from
ministry of resources
when seagram has been in the midst of
mayor
if your musical
you re general in brief
i recommend if you have read this
it describes
a lot of elsie coming in
lots of details not
so the key thing is if we go over
minn kota research tools
as those first box on the left here
and to protect research tools
you're going to see
anyplace where work research and tools
appearing
basis so it's not that i mean a lot
patsy for characterization of research
shows up
which isn't necessarily what i will be
looking for clues
search
but for example like titles if you're
working with tied
placement here at invent
as britain
all kinds of interesting right on ca
to work with
trying to understand what we should or
shouldn't do what i did
and frankfurt resources for you won't
get to san pedro jackpots
seal final presentations whatever
research tool
jump all over town page
and we'll take a quick peter it was here
if there was a special mike if you want
to have trouble behind the scenes like
what should be glued on this page or
propose material you can always put on
that
for discussion
you can start writing stuff
refused to listen
here doesn't have to be the most amazing
taxed ever to be helpful to wiki
at the bundy summary of
they say kicked off
and then you can hit show preview
if you just type text
textile peer so you don't have to be
receipt powerful smart about
how to make the kids pages of things
even tougher a pretty fancy
i don't know how to do that someone else
did
but it doesn't mean that you can't
contribute just reattached
so if you just a second year in
baltimore and work
so once you see that you which she wants
done
if we wanna make something
bolti can highlight it please the couple
tool to help you
which he has a special markup
entity but
single
quotes around some textile either side
that text becomes bolts
if you do something
to single cause it becomes a talents
you can insert lengths
keeping evening has a little seemed sure
things like
really weird person stuff
is trying to be there at the event
icon for signature
this really weird character here
it's like two dash is it
for children's
it turn into
your name
with the date and time
say page
there's no begin that discussion
it's completely pointless
what is the way he took a hit work
sometimes just ripe age
you could always treat yourself
maturity in the past
and just reconcile it's okay to try
things out
to go back to page
you can
hit added for the whole thing
you'll see the whole thing
anneke screw-up
accidentally hope eight
that we have all of the old versions
survived acts that would lead a whole
bunch of stuff
and want it back
if we could go to history button
all the old versions of their so if you
want to go back and see
this version that was from
poppers won't go
there's the old version
it gives you a special wake up here was
really weird idea number
this case they were going to change it's
always in history
so we have every version of it repays
somebody
to eat something in the new one
it's it's still there
with this class
i'm not there were too much about the
details of
all the things that would be a day
i would probably get as you go you start
making the pages
patent gaza triceps here if you want to
add wikipedia and making a little better
they for example hound
we do
tickets sold wikipedia
lucite beads song
debates
if you know anything about what to do so
marks there's a lot more to say about
movie stars in this little tiny page
and i thought i read through there were
a couple of
things wrong
you know they were relieved way both
names are
you can go ahead please
but sometimes a little scary jump in
wikipedia
i've made some edits and some other came
along
that's okay
you can try things out that you said in
the wiki
pete i page pierce ego
right here on cam lessons in really
crazy
and general works i didn't do anything
to stop acrobats felon
it's okay
iraqi creative wikipedia page
your personality
lots of liked it
and copy to yet
so the place to try something out
if you've got some interesting
the other countries might want anterior
about
things are secure country because
there's a lot was part of the time
frontier l_d_p_ page
fill it up here
with pictures
ordeal
and then was like it
since then
burden because
i did one four
a big nasa scientists and i didn't want
him to see my address
i really want to see a final pretty page
that looks very nice and how
writeformatting i didn't do that
so i did all our
internal
sophie search for
peters yes
their security staff
although insert
kenneth broken but that's ok notice
trying to figure out
i want to have some get taxed
and some basic points
and have a few months before apple
so this guy rental nasa missions that i
was on
and
so we're going to use this throughout
the class i'm going to be adding
and taking notes in his working today
we have some time
so that in time
so we're going to go ahead and login
too
the class
amber and start using the command line
and so i think this would be the most of
our people logged into computers
incomparable
this is the first time we've done
something
i don't think this is what we do in the
wiki
if you guys
anything else that don't work for you
and
a lot of times
elston
i wasn't seriously confused
of patients and their
tobacco and
and we'll get going on actually using
less and trying out
in the commitments that it takes
a long time to get to know all the
details
of how to get around
command-line
and use the fashionable
remember
went camping spots i might have been
doing this for twenty years
but you see everyone who can teach you
something
there are so many tools inlets
and michelle's
and things like that right
everyone of you can teach me something
to eat spots there
that's just part of the video
tadalafil bashful about talking about
things and figure out
how do you want to hear
african tried networks that uh... is
online
really what place to start it might
actually be better
so i'm not gonna show you the perfect
solution
mostly anyway
to get things done
and socio you could use of the stuff in
uh... cygwin on windows
happen fast walk was it
does it work
it gets a little talks on
i'm hoping that that he has listened to
your phone barman
you can take with you
ambiental
i'll give you the file
that actually gives you the survey you
can take home
one two three
for the rest of
along
vmware supports
so they should be able to take this with
you if you're using
pop up
i've taken on other countries
has just shown
through the end of the properties active
army
cost recording
in finding out that you don't
something that
can't figure out
so on your desktop
there should be
technical type
cut his or windows version
product approval caucasus h secure shell
and it was one of the first
shells
inverted everything going across
uh... you know
what do what you do is you can get in
server every text that you tried
near here or go to the server
and anybody who can
wrapping up traffic
the deadlock between the computer and
server
so that way if you don't have to work
things like that it's all protected
uh... there are other ways to connect
the servers unfortunately when each
will actually try to teach you something
never hear it worked on it
deceitful
if i could have put it out
and herbal picture
out some of our people
frightens people stop using telnet are
shown
spousal support probably
your occurred
opposite
we cannot do that
entities for here
market
anonymously
yugoslav at your password
user
one-stop such perhaps
and repair low points
undergoes
your password
it's possible
that your environment
is the way so many people
excuses enjoyed
was supposed to be safe
my security if you were a bit
those two things went there
st
that translates
equal
let's see
surrendering buddy
and you all others
and he used to sit waiting on windows
it's quite ok
this park i think you know
one and it's my job to meet you guys
comparable
your job is is that for all interested
and if things are confusing that's okay
we're confidence that you know
again again throughout the semester
trying to make it so that the county
it's not easy material
if we see again again
also was slowly sinking in
and you'll get in on what's
when you finally realize how it works
executives will strive to embody
and for the hosting
research
tools see column
any
alone do you see the connection fights
the only one you want to deal with this
as the states
say that's awesome
and it's a
so don't sit here is one of your saved
i think it's important
can fall you'll on our computers at the
switch computers
alias isn't going to be there for your
personal computers and your
workstations if your receipt on student
here
that will stay on workstation they won't
comes from computers with
go ahead and click
let's go ahead
hands
just double click back and you should
see something like this
please double click the research tools
and here
lucy
weed
the chipmunks actress lauren
bridges
she still treated as a
cost but he was he said yes to
well
middlesex since it was good
strikes again
i and tried again and went
i don't understand
it's possible or network pickup
or party has some new
should be able to them
eaters point writer c company
or signals
uh... said
the mouse yes
pasta obsolete
it's not like that
he tried to things around
it's not going
this is a patrolman
there's no practical
and you can convince the serbs
getting very different for you guys
hopefully you'll survive
sorrento contractual commitments
we had ten warheads here so we're gonna
give it a go and see how far we could
get
and we're gonna keep yourself patrick
cox
uh... so if you don't get the first time
that's expected
follow along
c
so the first time and i met you guys
this once more just fine
uh... because lineup who's walked into
the computer
and there's a lot
bizarre
exporters
you can see who's around
you might use this if you're working
late night
you want to see who's also want to try
and say hey
andrea star
marc's luke and john oklahoma
more importantly bell you want to know
what senior director in
so ls
list files
and still is really an exciting
alice
aptitude
marcus allen
surely all
stuff
ngos
concedes the words in your career
and i'll show you some
so please get back
collapsed actually
there's extra stuff
the search for the period
mustache analyzed
we're gonna get outlawed
purist wave slope
and i think you guys
pretty complicated stuff
gets
pc
ellis
morningside
the latter alf
it occurred
he wants al fayed
what business dealings with the local
posse
this is the permission
are really great
uh... agreed to pop
who've been
detects directory
for was unit
biased one sided
so
which where
too dot
dr
and what's that
startup securities
directly at odds
decorated
this is the folder
inside out
decreases
week police in sight
it's all of you guys
that's not what it's like to get rid of
dot
the files watching
ceo
so i think
and then there's a bunch of people
tomorrow file
egbert
so etiquette
sorrento
lectures
elaborate
and feel free to ask me questions isn't
a lot
three directory you need to get together
today if you
i would also do some comments as we go
home
anything is starts with that
discount character
and we're sorry
is a comment
so i can type
tell us
this lewis
files
uh... everything from that
combat coming on
let's try and define testify also work
with
there's a command call talks
doesn't seem very useful took before
they start off
you'll find all kinds of weird times
would you like pulp untouched
with processes
free to file does not exist
or to update the time
so if we say touch
mine ship
and now we have a file
call my ship
and if you look here
it's zero
zero i think that it's terrible
missing your old records on the syrup
forearms thank you regards
tested request
we're going to break the response of
state
so we can create
another file it's a touch
if we do in their own special
we now have two files another ship and
my ship
listed many articles have looked at
induced so we can say
we got sick reason folders authority
create a folder
those files
their anything you want them to keep
exam
could mean a future lectures
file types of file names are not
certainly associated
so what's your final thoughts on this
side
he said he thought was really a ticket
info databases that fifty
candle internationally watson
rarefied and streetdirectory and katie
org
ants
picture
now watchdog anti-pollution here
on links
things are case sensitive please by all
means
i can also maker
and if we do a listing
we now have
another folder and therefore
that is same exact characters
properties in lower case
coming toward you right now i'll keep
warning throughout the semester
don't do this
because the target of the windows
workflow mac
those two files organising bang
i don't know what was going to win forms
that life that's probably true
the most important stuff
that's also going to just like a
mandatory
d_r_
remove directories
and will say another folder
attache equipped recovery is a lot so if
i go back to you
handle
right here and i have to tab ki
his friend left hand side there
the shuttle still trying to protect
informed
since then try and help you out
legalistic
dance is done
yesterday older
on it
shakespeare's self
there are any notes
post-cold-war were collected institute
if you're a etsy com
different here right now
at some point sources from
sometime today or tomorrow
files
sort of at least ads
casey market yet for the first few times
there's a lot
at first bears a striking anyways
but there are a views article
historic online wednesday
everything you see here at all politics
is working together
so picky for
dreadful
you should have
it was on its own
this is the exact opposite
everything he wants to work together
originally were not
bns into work with most of it
the control officer
and so every time you want something new
it's sorts incremental single gets
bigger and bigger scientology
any goal is to make things together so
that
you can say premiums and it would censor
pickup parts you want while
get rid of kidney because of the season
has temporarily
so these little pieces
suggest
so let me ask you guys
right sanje tha
last searches
two spots
forgets how are you reading
sent to him
experts
greater on